<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life Consulting Group on Life Consulting Group LLC</title>
    <link>http://micro-co.stackstaging.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Life Consulting Group on Life Consulting Group LLC</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 15:58:45 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://micro-co.stackstaging.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Thankyou</title>
      <link>http://micro-co.stackstaging.com/thankyou/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 15:30:16 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://micro-co.stackstaging.com/thankyou/</guid>
      <description>ANALYZE &amp;#8226; OPTIMIZE &amp;#8226; GROW  Thanks for your message. We&#39;ll reply as soon as possible.
HOME
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Consulting</title>
      <link>http://micro-co.stackstaging.com/corporateconsulting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 13:51:09 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://micro-co.stackstaging.com/corporateconsulting/</guid>
      <description>HOME &amp;gt; CORPORATE CONSULTING   If your company has been growing quickly there may be systems and policies you’ve overlooked or outgrown. Businesses from all sectors work with Life Consulting Group to streamline their processes, troubleshoot problem areas, and lay the foundations for long-term success.
  OUR SERVICES REGULATORY
REQUIREMENTS     We help you understand your responsibilities and ensure you have the right policies and procedures to be legally compliant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Support</title>
      <link>http://micro-co.stackstaging.com/startupsupport/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 08:36:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://micro-co.stackstaging.com/startupsupport/</guid>
      <description>HOME &amp;gt; STARTUP SUPPORT   Entrepreneurs from many industries work with Life Consulting Group to make sure they have an efficient, compliant business that’s primed for growth. Investing in the right team supported by lean systems allows the business to grow smoothly while you focus on what you’re good at.
  OUR SERVICES TAKING FIRST
STEPS     From developing a business plan to deciding how to implement your ideas, we help you take the first steps to make your idea a reality.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>